yes can you tell the people what negging means no can you tell the people okay so negging from
my understanding is basically when a guy knows he knows that you're beautiful he knows that you're
a star that's what drew him to you in the first place but he finds little ways to chip out your
self-esteem he might find little faults or he will try to highlight things that he knows that you
might not be necessarily as good at or as confident in and he will make you feel like you're not good
enough in his presence or he will do things like overloading you with compliments and acting like
he's so in awe of you and then sometimes he would just like detach out of nowhere you feel this sense
of uncertainty and this all falls under the umbrella of negging because it's this man's intention to
control the way that you see yourself but also to control the way that you see him he wants you
to see him as the star yep because he sees you as the star it's so it's so up and they also do it in
a version where they will take something that you really care about and undermine it
so
you